<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Acadiverse Mobile</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="msg_account_permabanned">Your account has been permanently banned for repeatedly or severely violating our Code of Conduct. The specific reason given was: $1. If you believe that you were banned in error, you can go to http://acadiverse.magizile.xom/account/appeal to appeal this ban.</string>
    <string name="msg_account_tempbanned">Your account has been banned until $1 for the following reason: $2.</string>
    <string name="msg_banned_from_chat">You may not perform this action as you are currently banned from sending chat messages/PMing users who are not moderators. Please contact us if you believe that this is a mistake.</string>
    <string name="msg_blank_password">Please enter your password.</string>
    <string name="msg_blank_username">Please enter your username.</string>
    <string name="msg_block_user_confirmation">Are you sure you wish to block this user? They will not be able to send you any PMs or comment on your submissions, and they will also be automatically blocked from any chats that you owm!</string>
    <string name="msg_block_user_from_chat_confirmation">Are you sure you wish to block this user from this chat? They will not be able to send any more chat messages!</string>
    <string name="msg_blocked_from_chat">This action could not be performed because you have been blocked from this chat. Please contact one of the chat moderators if you believe that this is in error.</string>
    <string name="msg_chat_deleted">This action could not be perfoemed as the chat has been deleted. Chats can be deleted by the owner, or they can be deleted by an Acadiverse moderator or an admin for violating the Terms of Service or Code of Conduct.</string>
    <string name="msg_connection_error">Failed to connect to the server. Please check your Internet connection. Our servers may also be down; if this is the case, please wait a few minutes and/or try again later.</string>
    <string name="msg_delete_message_confirmation">Are you sure you wish to delete this message? This can NOT be undone!</string>
    <string name="msg_incorrect_password">Your password is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="msg_incorrect_username">No account exists with this username.</string>
    <string name="msg_logout_confirmation">Are you sure you wish to log out?</string>
    <string name="msg_not_enough_money">You cannot afford this item. It costs $1 Acadicoins and you currently have $2.</string>
    <string name="msg_not_enough_reputation_points">You need at least $1 Reputation Points to perform this action.</string>
    <string name="msg_pm_user_blocked">You cannot PM this user because they have blocked you.</string>
    <string name="msg_pm_user_opted_out">You cannot PM this user because they have chosen not to receive PMs from users who are not moderators.</string>
    <string name="msg_private_chat_insufficient_permissions">This action could not be performed because the chat is private and you have not been given the appropriate permissions to access it.</string>

    <string name="msg_problem_with_credentials">You have been logged out as there is a problem with your credentials.</string>
    <string name="msg_report_confirmation">You are about to report $1 for the following reason: $2. Please note that reports are taken very seriously, and that sending false reports may result in a ban. Proceed with reporfting this user?</string>
    <string name="msg_slur_entered">This action could not be performed because your message contains a racial slur. You have earned a strike for this action. If you attempt to send such messages $1 more times, you will be banned from chatting/sending PMs.</string>
    <string name="msg_swear_word_entered">This action could not be performed because your message contains bad language or suggestive content. You have earned a strike for this action. If you attempt to send such messages $1 more times, you will be banned from chatting/sending PMs.</string>
    <string name="msg_too_many_chat_strikes">You have been automatically banned from sending chat/PMs because you have attempted to send a chat message/PM with swear words or racial/cultural slurs in it too many times.</string>
    <string name="msg_wrong_account_type">This feature is only available to $ accounts.</string>

    <string name="str_account_typpe_student">Student</string>
    <string name="str_account_type_parent">Parent</string>
    <string name="str_account_type_teacher">Teacher</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
</resources>
